uberchar.com 2013-04-03

# 

By using our services and accessing our Site (www.uberchar.com), you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this statement, as modified from time to time by us.

Your trust is our most valuable asset. We safeguard that trust by keeping your non-public personal information or personally identifiable information as well as user content and material (called "data" herein) in a secure environment. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you.

If you have any questions about our privacy statement or our use of your data or if you need help changing or deleting your account you can e-mail us at **legal(a)uberchar.com**

#### 1.- Information Collection

We may collect the following data about you and/or your use of our Site:

  * Data we receive from you when you signup, request a service, or file a claim, such as name, surname, address, country, email, birthdate, genre and other information about your preferences and/or interests.
  * Data about your activity in our Site and/or affiliated companies, and/or related intermediaries in order to create access statistics and/or market research.
  * In some cases, data concerning your visits to our Site and may include your ip address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our Site, session number and user ID.

#### 2.- Information Use

Except as disclosed in this statement, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies our users personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly without our users' consent. We may use, sell, disclose, or otherwise dispose of the data we collect in the following circumstances:

Internal Analysis and Promotions. We may use information about you for our own internal statistical, design, operational purposes such as to estimate our audience size; measure aggregate traffic patterns; and understand demographic, customer interest, purchasing and other trends among our users and customers.

Legal Requirement. We may disclose user data:

(a) to conform with the law, respond to claims or comply with legal process.

(b) to protect and defend our or our user's rights or property, our Site, our employees, guests or the public, including fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Site.

(c) if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

Company Sale. All information collected through our Site is considered a trade secret of Uberchar. As the owner of such information, we may disclose or sell such information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale to a third party of our company or a portion of our assets.

Aggregate Information. We collect Aggregate Information about you and your use of our Site whenever you visit us online. For instance, we may collect various forms of "click stream" information such as entry and exit points for our Site (i.e., referring URLs or domains), site traffic statistics, page views, impressions, and operating system and browser type. In addition, when users request pages on our Site, our servers automatically log their IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web.

We also may use third-party software that tracks traffic directed to our Site from affiliate web sites and the purchases that result from this traffic. This information is aggregated and is not tied to an individual purchase.

This Aggregate Information generally will not personally identify you or be correlated to you individually for external purposes. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user, and will not be used to contact you. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, such information will be treated like any other personal information under this statement.

Notwithstanding any preference that you select, we may contact you from time to time to provide services that you have requested or for customer service matters, such as responding to service-related inquiries, updating our policies, notifying you of changes to existing services or new Site functionalities.

#### 3.- Cookies and Web Beacons

We may make use of "cookies" on our Site. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user's device by a Web server based on the permissions set in a user's browser software. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's device (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the Web site that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the device and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. Therefore, cookies only identify the user's device to the Web site which may correlate other information, including personally identifying information, with the cookie.

We may use cookies to allow us to automate access and data entry functions of our Site such as to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the Site (if any), tailor the Site to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track use of the Site to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not thereby enabling us to improve and update the Site effectively.

We also may use third party advertisements on our Site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our Site, which will also send these advertisers information that may include your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our Site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You may adjust your Web browsers to either alert you of the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. Be aware that if you elect not to accept cookies, our Site may not function properly or permit access.

We may use Web beacons on our Site or other sites and may permit third parties to place them on our Site to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes. A Web beacon, also known as a "Web bug," is a small, graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or in an e-mail message that is designed to allow the site owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a site. Web beacons are often invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the Web page, document or e-mail message. Web beacons are represented as HTML IMG tags in the Web page; users can click on "view profiles" of the web page to see whether the page is using a web beacon.

Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons can also be linked to personal information. For example, advertising networks use Web beacons to add information to a personal profile of what sites a person is visiting and to determine what banner ads to display based on the profile. Another use of Web beacons is to provide an independent accounting of how many people have visited a particular Web site. Web beacons are also used to gather statistics about Web browser usage at different places on the Internet.

#### 4.- Links

Please be aware that we and/or our users provide links to third-party Web sites and that we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites.

We encourage you to review and understand the legal notice, terms of use, site agreement or similar named link appearing on any site that you visit through our Site before providing them with information. These sites may be not under our control and may have different terms and conditions from these.

#### 5.- Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We restrict access to data about you to those employees whom we know have a valid business purpose to have access to such data to provide products or services to you. We provide training and communications programs to our employees. These programs educate them on the meaning and requirements of our strict standards for data security and confidentiality. We require those who provide services for us and to whom we may provide your data to abide by the same security restrictions.

#### 6.- Responsibility

Uberchar is not the publisher or author of the user content. It is a passive service for storage and dissemination of the information, material, ideas and opinions that Uberchar users may choose to distribute, publish, transmit or display as user content.

Unless otherwise noted, all materials on this Site are protected as the copyrights, trade dress, trademarks and/or other intellectual properties owned by Uberchar and/or its subsidiaries and affiliates or by other parties. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.

Your use of the materials included on this Site is for informational purposes only. You agree you will not distribute, publish, transmit, modify, display or create derivative works from or exploit the contents of this Site in any way. You may not copy, distribute or display materials on this Site or any part of it to third parties. No other use, reproduction or distribution is permitted without prior written permission. Any infringement of these rights will result in appropriate legal action. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Uberchar for any and all unauthorised uses you may make of any material on the Site. You acknowledge the unauthorised use of the contents could cause irreparable harm to Uberchar and that in the event of an unauthorised use, Uberchar shall be entitled to an injunction in addition to any other remedies available at law or in equity.

You need a user name and/or email and password (access data) for full access to our Site. You must provide complete and accurate information as requested on the signup form. You shall be responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your access data and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your session. Access data are for your personal use only and are non-transferable. You may not use a third party's access data at any time. You agree to notify us immediately If you have reason to believe your access data have been compromised or there has been any unauthorized use of your account.

You agree you are and shall remain solely responsible for the contents of any submissions you make, and you will not submit material that is unlawful, defamatory, abusive or obscene. You agree that you will not submit anything to the Site that will violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s).

While we appreciate your interest in Uberchar, we do not want and cannot accept any ideas you consider to be proprietary regarding designs, product technology or other suggestions you may have developed. Consequently, any material you submit to this Site will be deemed a grant of a royalty free non-exclusive right and license to dispose these materials in the conditions provided in this Legal Notice.

Uberchar is not liable to you or any third party for any errors or delays in the content of the Site or for any actions taken in reliance on it. To the fullest extent allowed by applicable law, Uberchar will not be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential loss arising from the use of the content contained in this Site or from your access of other material on the Internet via web links from this Site. Uberchar uses reasonable skill and care in developing this Site but does not give any warranty as to its accuracy, availability or reliability nor does Uberchar guarantee that the functions contained in the Site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that this Site or its server will be free of viruses or other harmful components, or that defects will be corrected even if Uberchar is aware of them.

Our Site is a general audience site that is not designed nor intended to collect data from children under the age of 14. To respect the privacy of children, signup on our Site is not allowed for children under the age of 14. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

If Uberchar's technical staff finds that files or processes belonging to a user pose a threat to the proper technical operation of the system or to the security of other users, Uberchar reserves the right to delete those files or to stop those processes. If we suspect a user access data are being used by someone who is not authorized by the proper user, we may temporarily disable that user access in order to preserve system security. In all such cases we will contact the user as soon as feasible.

Uberchar reserves the right to refuse service and/or to cancel user access at any time automatically without notice if any of the terms or conditions of this Legal Advice are breached.

#### 7.- Changes to this Legal Notice

We reserve the right to modify this legal notice at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our Site.

#### 8.- User rights

Upon receiving your written request, Uberchar shall provide you any classified data about you, according to the provisions of local laws on protection of personal data. The right of access to personal data may be exercised by the interested party free of charge as long as such information is requested no more than once every year, unless a legitimate interest to do otherwise is evidenced. If any piece of information is incorrect, or you wish to update or remove any of them, we will correct, update or remove such information at no cost whatsoever for you. For that purpose, please send an e-mail to **legal(a)uberchar.com** stating in the subject field "Inform Data", "Modify Data", "Remove Data" and/or "Update Data" as appropriate, together with the object of your request and we will attend to it as soon as feasible.

#### 9.- Applicable law

These terms and conditions are governed and will be interpreted in accordance with Spanish Law and any disputes relating to these terms and conditions will be exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of the Madrid (Spain) courts.

#### 10.- Company information

**Uberchar**  
Dr. Fleming 6  
28703 - San Sebastián de los Reyes  
Madrid - España  
**legal(a)uberchar.com**
